(laughs)
너네도 내 머리속을
볼 수 있다면 좋을 텐데
I wish you could all
be inside my head.
대화가 정말 흥미롭거든
The conversation is sparkling.
그래, 뭔지 알려주마
Fine, I'll tell you.
지의류는 균류와 조류의 공생체야
A lichen is an organism made
up of two separate species,
fungi and algae.
다른 종과 합친다 가정하고
If you could merge
with another species,
원하는 종을 고르고
이유를 대봐
what species would
you pick and why?
힌트를 주자면 정답은 하나야
Hint: There is a right answer.
너네는 못 맞춰
None of you will get it.
그렇다면 나는 백조로 할래
Okay, I'd pick swan because, uh,
the resulting hybrid
인간의 진화된 산업 문명과
would have the advanced
industrial civilization
전부터 갈망했던 길고
우아한 목을 가질 수 있어
of a human and
the long graceful neck
I've always dreamed of having.
틀렸어
레너드?
Wrong. Leonard?
말,
키 때문에
Horse, but mostly just
for the height.
생식기도 꽤 굵겠다
A little bit for
the genital girth.
틀렸어,
지저분한 얘기는 하지 말자
Wrong, and let's
keep it clean, shall we?
캥거루
Kangaroo, uh,
나는 캥거쥬가 되겠지
I'd be Kanga-Jew.
(chuckles)
유대인 중에 최초로
덩크슛을 한 사람이 될 거야
The first of my people
to dunk a basketball. (chuckles)
엄마 집에 얹혀 살지 않고
Also instead of just living
in your mother's house,
엄마 속에 살겠네
you could actually
live inside her body.
(mocking laugh)
나쁘지 않은데
그것도 틀렸어
Clever, but also wrong.
정답은 지의류야
No, the best organism for human
beings to merge with
is the lichen itself.
그러면 인간이면서
동시에 균류와 조류겠지
That way, you'd be human,
fungus, and algae.
3배로 위협적이야
Triple threat.
쓰리 빈 샐러드처럼
Like three-bean salad.
어떤 상황에서 유리한데?
Give me one circumstance in
which that would be useful.
상상해봐
All right, picture this:
야외 콘서트에서
a beautiful outdoor concert.
나는 인간으로
베토벤을 즐겨 듣지
Now, as a human,
I appreciate Beethoven.
단풍 나무에서 자라는 균류로
As a fungus,
I have a terrific view,
전망 좋은 곳을 차지하고
growing out of a
towering maple tree.
비싼 돈도 낼 필요 없어
And no thank you,
expensive concessions.
조류는 햇빛만 받으면 되니까
Because as an algae, I'll just
snack on this sunlight.
졌다, 졌어
- He got us again.
- No, he didn't.
주제를 바꿔도 괜찮다면
Anyway, if it's
okay with you,
하워드 총각 파티 얘기를 하자
we should talk about
Howard's bachelor party.
Oh, oh.
지의류 주제에 비해
흥미가 떨어지지만
Seems like a bit
of a letdown
after our lichen
conversation, but...
반 백조가 뭘 알겠어
What do you know,
you're half swan.
스트리퍼에 대해
알아봤는데
I've been doing
some research on strippers.
나이랑 장애에 관대하면
할인이 많이 된대
One agency I spoke to, said I
could get us a great price
if we're flexible on
age range and number of limbs.
재밌겠지만
Sounds like loads of fun,
베르나데트한테
스트리퍼는 없을거라 했어
but I promised Bernadette
no strippers.
넌 스트리퍼의 왕이잖아
You don't want strippers?
You're the king of strippers.
할리우드 클럽에 있는
봉도 네 이름을 따서 지었어
The one club in North Hollywood
named a pole after you.
이제 그런 건 별로야
What can I tell ya-- I'm not
into that stuff anymore.
하워드, 자랑스럽다
Good for you, Howard.
I'm proud of you.
그래도 우리 중에
처음으로 장가가는데
And still, you're the first one
of use to get married.
축하는 해줘야지
We have to do something special.
독일에는 재밌는 전통이 있어
You know Germans have an
interesting pre-wedding custom--
내 스타일은 아닌 것 같아
Well, it's probably not for me.
나파 밸리에 가면 어때?
Maybe we can go up to
Napa Valley.
와인 열차도 타 보고
They've got that wine train.
와인은 별로
Boo, wine!
열차는 좋아
But yay, trains. I'm in.
이 시기가 여행하기 좋아
Anyway, it's a beautiful
time of year.
포도원을 방문하고
Uh, you travel through
the vineyards.
기차에서는 와인
테이스팅이 있어
There's a tasting on board.
꽃도 활짝 피었지
And all the wildflowers
are in bloom.
환상적이야
Magic.
여자를 구하는 대신
여자가 됐네
Look at that, in 30 seconds,
we went from
hiring women to being them.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x22
The Stag Convergence
Original Air Date on April 26, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
오늘 총각 파티 한다며
So, I hear you and
the lost boys are having
a bachelor party tonight.
스테이크 먹고
위스키 마시려고
Yeah, just going to a
restaurant, get some steaks,
- 걱정할 거 없어
- 걱정이라니?
and scotch. Nothing to worry about.
Why should I worry?
총각 파티잖아
Well, I don't know.
It's a bachelor party.
스트리퍼도 올 수 있어
There could be strippers.
질투 나지 않아?
Wouldn't that make you
a little jealous?
레너드, 너니까 걱정 안해
Oh, come on Leonard, it's you.
What's going to happen?
스트리퍼가 있다면
I mean, even if
there was a stripper,
눈도 안 마주치고
all you'd do is avoid
eye-contact
혹시 아이가 과외
필요한지 물어볼 거잖아
and maybe offer to help
her kid with his homework.
난 성적 욕구가
피크를 찍고 있어
Hey, I am a young man
in his sexual prime.
조건만 주어진다면
Under the right conditions,
I-I-I am capable of just,
나도 막 나갈 수 있어
really crazy stuff.
여자랑 그런 적이 있긴 해?
Really? What is
the craziest thing
you've ever done with a woman?
우리가 바다에서
섹스한 건 제외하고
And the time you and I had sex
in the ocean does not count.
그걸 제외하면 안되지
Oh, come on.
That's got to count.
저류 때문에 죽을 수도 있었어
There was a really strong
undertow, we could have died.
아무튼 재밌게 놀아
Well, have fun tonight.
그래야지
Oh, I will.
무슨 일이 벌어질지 아무도 몰라
There is no telling
what might happen.
모르긴
(chuckling):
Yeah, there is.
남의 딸에게 SAT 과외를
해주는 건 좋은 일이라고
You know, there's
nothing wrong helping
some woman's kid
get through their S.A.T.'s.
라지가 준비를 잘했네
Hey, I got to hand it to Raj,
총각 파티를 하기에
장소가 딱이야
He found a really nice spot
to have a bachelor party.
나쁘지 않지
It's not bad.
기차랑 비교한다면 구리지만
Unless you compare it to
a train; then it stinks.
위스키 마시려고?
Are you drinking whiskey?
그럼
Indeed.
총각파티라는
사회적 관습에 참여하려면
If I'm to participate
in the social convention
구성 요소도 받아들여야지
that is the stag night, then I
must embrace all its components:
담배, 욕설, 그리고 술도
including tobacco,
swear words, and yes, alcohol.
Jeepers, 너무 쓰잖아
Jeepers! That's yucky.
벌써부터 J로
시작하는 욕을 하다니
Whoa, it's a little
early to start
dropping J-bombs,
don't you think?
Hey, you guys.
하워드 축하해주려고 왔구나
Oh, hey, Wil. Nice of you to
make it out tonight for Howard.
조지 타케이네
욕조 파티보단 낫지
Well, it was either
this or another
hot tub party at
George Takei's house.
조금 혼란스럽네
I'm confused.
우리가 화해한 이후로
I thought since our
reconciliation,
친구가 된 거 아니였어?
I was your friend
in this group.
하워드도 내 친구야
Oh, I'm friends
with Howard too.
Oh!
개나 소나 다 친구구나
I guess you're just
friends with anybody.
Aah!
있잖아, 레너드
Hey, uh, Leonard...
만화방에 사정이 안 좋아서
things are a little tight
at the comic book store.
내 이름으로 축의금 부탁할게
I might need some help covering
my share of the check.
그래, 걱정 마
Oh, yeah, no worries.
발레파킹 요금도
And maybe a few bucks
for the valet.
Oh, all right.
집에 가려면
기름값도 필요하고
And gas money to get home.
Yeah, sure.
Great.
할아버지가 차던 시계야
You know what? This is
my grandfather's watch.
Oh.
18K 금인데 유럽에서
전쟁 때 구했대
18-carat gold, got it
in Europe during the war.
멋지네
Wow, that's very nice.
Mm-hmm.
$100에 팔게
100 bucks and it's yours.
여러분
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hey, everybody!
주인공이 도착했습니다
The bachelor boy has arrived!
(chuckles)
ALL: ♪ For he's
a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ For he's a
jolly good fellow ♪
♪ For he's a jolly
good fellow ♪
♪ Which nobody can deny ♪
하워드는 좋은 놈이지
Yes, yes, yes.
He's a jolly good fellow.
스트리퍼는 언제 도착해?
What time do
the strippers arrive?
배리, 스트리퍼가 없는 파티야
Actually, Barry, we're not going
to have strippers tonight.
그럼 $200를 $1짜리로
바꿀 필요가 없었잖아
Ah, then what the frig did I get
200 dollars in singles out for?
내 시계 살래?
You want to buy a watch?
들러리 대표 에이미입니다
This is Maid of Honor
Amy Farrah Fowler,
몇 주 후의 결혼식을 앞두고
bringing you the
wedding activities
준비과정을 공개합니다
just weeks out from
the big day.
아름답고 눈 부시는 여성과
Let's check in with a beautiful,
radiant young woman,
옆에는 신부입니다
and her friend who's
about to get married.
지금 무엇을 하고 있나요?
Ladies, can you tell us
what you're doing?
기념품을 포장하고 있어
Um, these are gift bags
멀리서 온 하객 분들의
호텔에 두려고
we're going to put in the hotel
rooms of our out-of-town guests.
패서디나 지도
This is a map of Pasadena.
맛집 리스트
This is a list of
local restaurants.
하워드 친척을 위해서는
And then, for
Howie's relatives,
항히스타민제, 제산제
we have antihistamines,
antacids,
설사랑 변비 약도 있어
and medicine for diarrhea
and constipation.
'Stop'이랑 'go'로 표기했어
Yeah, we labeled them
"stop and go."
이제 중요한 질문입니다
AMY: All right, pivoting
to the big question:
결혼식 후 첫날밤을
치르게 될 텐데
Bernadette,
on your wedding night
you'll be consummating
your marriage.
어떤 체위로 진행할 예정인지?
What do you think your first
sexual position will be
as husband and wife?
Amy, please.
잡혀 살지 않으려면
탑 자리를 선점해야돼
Keeping in mind that
whoever's on top
may set the tone
for the marriage.
그만하자
Okay, show's over.
첫날밤에 애가
생길 수도 있는데
Hey, they may conceive a child
on their wedding night.
자신의 탄생 과정을
알면 재밌잖아
Don't you think
the kid might get a kick
out of knowing
how it happened?
관심 없어
I don't care.
하워드 성을 따를 건지 물어봐
Ask her things like "Are you
going to take Howard's name?"
누가 누구 위에
있는지는 몰라도 돼
Not "Who's going
to sit on who."
붙여 쓸가 생각하고 있어
I've actually been thinking
I'm going to hyphenate:
Bernadette Maryann
Rostenkowski-Wolowitz.
Nice.
닷컴 도메인도 미리 등록해놔
You know, you should totally get
Bernadette Maryann
Rostenkowski-Wolowitz.com
before someone snaps it up.
하워드가 벌써 샀지
Howard already
took care of it.
결혼 웹사이트도 만들었어
Plus, he set up our
beautiful wedding Web site
가족사를 재미있게 소개했더라
with cute little facts
about our family histories.
한때는 폴란드에서
우리 가족들이 이웃이였대
Do you know,
for a while in Poland,
my family and his family
were neighbors.
멋지네
Oh, that's cool.
아냐, 나중에 설명할게
No, it's not.
I'll explain it to you later.
(all laughing)
(clinking on glass)
자, 모두 주목합시다
May I have
your attention, please?
제 절친 하워드의
결혼을 축하하는 자리입니다
We are hear tonight to celebrate
the upcoming nuptials
of my best friend
Howard Wolowitz.
ALL:
Hear! Hear!
윌 휘튼의 절친이기도 하지
And, apparently,
Wil Wheaton's best friend.
쉘든
Sheldon...
내 손이랑 말해
Talk to the hand.
주인공에게 축하
메시지 전하실 분?
Does anyone
have any words
they'd like to say about
our man of the evening?
내가 할게
I do.
(all groan)
이런 자리에 알맞게
As is the tradition,
하워드를 놀리는
조크를 몇 개 준비해봤어
I have prepared a series of
disrespectful jokes
which generate humor
at Howard's expense.
너네 옆구리가
간지러울 거다
Prepare to have your ribs
tickled... (clears throat)
하워드, 네가 제일 늦게
결혼할 줄 알았어
Howard... I always thought
you'd be the last one of us
키도 작고 매력 없는 놈이라
to ever get married, because you
are so short and unappealing.
안 그래?
Am I right?
어디 보자
Let's see here.
이제는 좀 진지해질게
Oh, seriously though, Howard,
넌 내가 아는
사람 중 제일 똑똑해
you're actually one of the most
intelligent people I know.
이건 반어법이야
And that's a zinger,
because you're not.
(laughs)
언젠가는 좋은 남편이
될 날이 올 것 같았어
I've always thought
that you'd make
someone a fine husband someday.
부품을 제대로 구하고
Assuming you'd be able
to get the parts,
조립할 수 있는
기술을 갖춘다면
and develop the
engineering skills
거의 불가능하겠지만
to assemble them,
which I don't see as likely.
Hacha!
(laughs)
Okay... Let me see here.
농담은 그만하고
Okay, kidding aside--
하워드, 넌 좋은 친구야
Howard, you are a good friend.
행복하길 바랄게
And I wish you nothing
but happiness.
버징가, 뻥이야
Bazinga, I don't!
- 쉘든
- 더블 버징가, 진심이야
Sheldon...
Doubleazinga! I do!
날 따라잡을 수는 없겠군
Good luck
following that.
하워드가 드디어 장가가네
So, Howard Wolowitz
tying the knot.
총각으로 지낼 날이
얼마 안 남았어
Leaving his crazy
bachelor days behind.
뜨거웠던 시절이였지
He was a wild one.
우리 모두에게
Well, I guess
we all kind of were.
이런 적도 있었지
I remember this one time,
해변 데이트를 하다가
I was with this girl
at the beach.
바다에서 섹스를 했어
We were in the ocean and
we started making out.
대단했지
I know, it was crazy.
아쿠아 양말도 안 신고
I wasn't even wearing
my Aquasocks.
Then...
관심 없어
Nobody cares, Hofstadter.
빨리 끝내
Wrap it up.
그래
Right.
하워드를 위하여
To Howard.
위하여
ALL:
To Howard.
난 바다에서 섹스했다고
I totally had sex
in the ocean.
내 차례
Okay, I'll go.
하워드랑 베르나데트가
Howard, when I think about you
and Bernadette
새로운 출발을 할 생각에
starting this wonderful life
together,
목이 메이네
I can't help but
get a little choked up.
I mean...
널 봐봐
look at you.
넌 모든 걸 가졌어
You have everything.
그리고 날 봐
Look at me.
난 37살이야
I'm 37.
가게 뒷방에서 살고
I sleep in the back of
a comic book store,
골밀도는 80살 노인과 같아
and I have the bone density
of an 80-year-old man.
하워드를 위하여
(whispers):
To Howard.
위하여
Yeah, to Howard.
Yes...
다음은 누구야?
Um, uh, who's next?
KRIPKE: I'll go.
모두가 생각하고 있지만
Howard, I'm gonna say something
to you that everybody's thinking
용기가 없어서
말을 안 하고 있어
but no one has the courage
to say out loud.
총각 파티를 할거면
When you invite a man
to a bachelor party,
당연히 스트리퍼가 있어야해
the implication is,
there will be strippers.
완전 나체는 아니더라도
Maybe not completely nude,
젖꼭지 가리개랑
지스트링 정도
but at least pasties
and G-strings.
많은걸 바라지 않아
That's not unreasonable.
옳소
KOOTHRAPPALI: Hear, hear.
ALL: Hear, hear.
또 누구 남았어?
Okay, uh, anybody else?
없나?
Huh? No?
신랑 들러리 차례네
Okay, it all comes down
to me, the best man.
(laughs)
그래스호퍼를 마셨더니
정신 없내
Ooh! This grasshopper is
kicking my ass-hopper.
미국에 처음 왔을 때
Okay, okay, when I first
came to this country,
어떻게 행동해야 하는지
뭘 입어야 하는지
I-I didn't know how to
behave or how to dress,
뭐가 쿨한지 몰랐어,
외롭더라고
or what was cool...
I was pretty lonely.
그런데 하워드를 만나고
인생이 바뀌었어
But then I met Howard, and
suddenly, my life changed,
같이 외로울 수 있었으니까
because we could
be lonely together.
이 남자가 내 전부가 되었어
This man became
my whole world.
잘 들었다, 프랜신
Yeah, nice speech, Francine.
아직 안 끝났지만 고마워
I'm not done,
but thank you.
돌이켜보면
I think back....
좋은 추억이 많았지
...to all the good times
we had, like, uh,
한번은 캠핑을 가서
when we went camping
and spent that night
서로 비밀을 공유했지
telling each other
all our secrets.
내 페디큐어 중독에
대해서 말하고
I told him I'm addicted
to pedicures
하워드는 사촌이랑
처음 관계를 가졌다고 했어
and he told me he lost his
virginity to his cousin.
(all laugh)
6촌이였어
She was my second cousin.
성적으로 처음
실망시킨 여자네
And the first woman you ever
disappointed sexually.
Ba-da-bazinga!
레너드랑 셋이서
라스베가스에 갔을 때는
Oh... oh, yeah, and then
there was the time
when Leonard and I took
Howard to Las Vegas
매춘부에게 팁을 주고
유대인인 척 하라고 했어
and paid a hooker to
pretend she was Jewish
작은 코셔 피클이
탐난다고 말하라고 시켰어
and that she wanted
his little kosher pickle.
(all laugh)
하워드가 매춘부를
따먹는 얘기 중에
Of all the "Howard
humping hookers" stories,
이게 최고야
that one's my favorite!
자, 여기까지
Okay, buddy, that's it.
Sit down.
코믹콘에서 세일러문
복장을 입었던 애도 있었지
Oh, oh, what about
that tubby girl
in the Sailor Moon
costume at Comic-con?
기억 안 나
Don't remember.
Please sit down.
내 인생 유일한 쓰리썸이었어
The only threesome
I've ever had in my life,
자랑스럽게도
이 놈이랑 같이 했지
and I'm proud to say it was
with this man right here.
(all laugh)
이제 조용히 좀 해
Oh, please shut up.
오해하지 마
Oh, oh, don't get me wrong,
우리끼리는
아무 짓도 안 했어
nothing happened with
me and Howard.
100킬로 나가는
세일러문이 중간에 끼었거든
There was about 200 pounds
of Sailor Moon between us.
(laughter)
좋은 건 인터넷에 공유해야지
Oh, Internet, this is
so going all over you.
Jeepers, 취한 것 같아
Jeepers, I'm drunk.
(both laugh)
데리러 와서 고마워
Thank you for picking us up.
위스티 병에 경고가 있더라
There's a warning, right there,
on the scotch bottle.
쳐마신 후에는
중장비를 다루지 말라고
(Scottish accent): You cannot be
operatin' heavy machinery
after you had a snootful
of this, laddie!
(both laughing)
재밌네
Funny.
잘 놀았어?
You boys have a nice time?
응
Yeah, it was great.
약속한 것처럼
Low-key, like I promised.
스트리퍼도 없었어
No hanky-panky, no strippers.
남자들끼리 모여서
얘기만 했지
Just the guys telling jokes.
좋았겠네
That's nice.
넌 어땠어?
How about you?
Did you have a fun night?
선물 포장하고
와인 마시고
Yeah, we, uh, made
gift bags, had wine,
웹서핑을 하다가
이걸 발견했어
and then went online
and saw this.
하워드가 매춘부를
따먹는 얘기 중에
KOOTHRAPPALI: Of all the "Howard
humping hookers" stories,
이게 최고야
that one's my favorite.
여기서 우리 집은 가까운데
You know, we're not that far
from my apartment.
세워주면 걸어갈게
If you stop the car,
I can walk from here.
가긴 어딜 가, 쓰리 웨이
You ain't goin'
anywhere, Threeway.
- 베르나데트, 들어봐
- 넌 거짓말을 했어
Bernadette, listen...
You lied to me.
과거를 다 밝혔다고 했지만
You said you told me about all
the girls you've been with,
사촌이나 매춘부,
그리고 라지 얘기도 없었어
but you never mentioned your
cousin, the prostitute or Raj!
차 안 세워도 돼
Seriously, you don't even have
to stop the car.
20km/h 밑으로만 가면
Anything under ten miles an hour
알아서 굴러 나갈게
and I can combat-roll
into the street.
확실하게 해두자
Okay, just to set
the record straight,
매춘부는 내가 부른게 아니라
라지가 선물로 준 거야
I didn't hire the prostitute,
she was a gift from him.
라지, 부끄러운 줄 알아
Shame on you, Raj.
여자들을 그렇게 대하면 안돼
That is not how we treat
women in this country.
핑계 대지 마
Don't you try and
blame this on him.
- 고마워, 베르나데트
- 닥쳐, 이 변태야
- Thank you, Bernadette.
- Zip it, pervert!
어떡해야 하는지 모르겠어
I don't know what
I'm going to do.
몇 주 후면 결혼식인데
I'm supposed to marry Howard
in a couple weeks
확신이 서지 않아
and I'm not sure I even know
who the man is anymore.
뭐가 제일 걸리는데?
I'm curious
what's bothering you most:
근친상간, 매춘부, 아니면
만화 캐릭터를 포함한 쓰리썸?
the borderline incest,
the prostitute or group sex
with the girl dressed as
the children's cartoon?
에이미, 도움 되는
말만 하기로 했잖아
Amy, remember when
we went over things
that would be helpful
and things that wouldn't?
맞다
Right.
- 방금 한 말은...
- 아니였어
- And that was...
- Not.
하워드는 순수한 줄 알았어
When I first met Howard,
he seemed so innocent to me,
엄마를 모시고 사는
다정한 남자
just a sweet little guy who
lives with his mother.
그게 네 이상형이라면
Well, if that's what
you like, I'll take you
만화방에 데리고 갈게
그런 남자는 널려 있어
to the comic book store--
the place is full of 'em.
그러고 보니
Wait a minute.
하워드는 네가 소개해줬지
You set me up with Howard.
그런 과거도 알고 있었어?
Did you know about
all the creepy stuff
he was into?
소문은 들었지
Well, a little.
You hear stuff...
왜 말 안 해줬어?
Why didn't you tell me
그러려고 했어
Well, I was gonna,
but I didn't think
첫 데이트로
끝날 줄 알았거든
it would go past
the first date.
하워드 엄마를 만나면
끝날 줄 알았고
Then, when it did,
I thought for sure
it wouldn't go past
you meeting his mother.
둘이 자는 건
상상도 못한 일이야
Definitely not past the
two of you sleeping together.
알아보지 못한 네 잘못이야
I mean, the warning signs were
there-- this is really on you.
God!
널 친구로 생각했는데
I thought you were
my friend.
(crying)
(sighs)
(door slams)
너도 별 도움 안 되네
I don't think
that was helpful.
베르나데트, 나야
Hi, Bernie, it's me again.
꼭 전화줘
Please call me back.
정말 미안해
Dude, I am so sorry.
네 잘못 아냐
It's not your fault,
it's mine.
다 내가 한 짓이지
I did all that stuff,
not you.
그 중 하나는 같이 했잖아
Actually, you did do
one of them together.
마셔
Here.
이건 뭔데?
What is this?
기분이 안 좋잖아
You're upset.
마실 것을 대접하라고 배웠어
The convention is to
bring an upset person
a hot beverage.
뭔데?
No, but what is it?
닭 육수야
Chicken broth.
문화적으로 적합한 것 같았어
It seemed culturally
appropriate.
주방에 치킨스톡 큐브가
딱 하나 남아서 처리했어
Also, there was a single cube
of chicken bouillon
in the cupboard when I moved in
8년 전에 이사왔을 때부터
and it's been bothering me
for the last eight years...
일석이조랄까
So, as they say, two birds.
이젠 어떡하지
I don't know what
my next move is.
하워드, 난 여자를 잘 몰라
Well, Howard, I don't know
much about women...
- 응?
- 그게 끝이야
- Yeah?
- No, uh, that, that's it.
난 여자를 잘 몰라
I don't know much about women.
라지, 넌 할말 있어?
Raj, you got anything?
코믹콘에서 만났던
여자 연락처는 있는데
I've got the phone number of
the tubby girl from Comic-Con.
걔한테 연락 안해
I'm not calling the
girl from Comic-con.
그래
All right.
세일러문은 혼자
즐길 수 있겠군
More Sailor Moon for me.
총각파티를
토해버렸어
I just threw up
the bachelor party.
베르나데트, 나와
Please come out, Bernadette.
얘기 좀 하자
Let's talk through this.
내버려둬
BERNADETTE:
No, leave me alone.
하워드한테 당한 대로
갚아주면 어때?
Perhaps you should give him
a taste of his own medicine.
잘생긴 사촌 없어?
Do you have a cousin
who you find attractive?
에이미
(knocking on door)
Amy.
네 소개로 만났잖아
Hey, you introduced him
to the sleazebag.
뒤처리는 해야지
I'm just trying to
clean up your mess.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
베르나데트랑 할 말이 있어
I need to talk to Bernadette.
지금은 안 만나 줄 거야
Well, I don't think she wants
to talk to anyone right now.
말 좀 전해줄래?
All right, well, could you
at least give her a message?
그래
Yeah, sure, I guess.
정말 미안하고
Tell her I'm really sorry.
결혼에 대한 생각이
바뀌었다면 이해할게
And if she doesn't want
to marry me, I get it.
이것만은 말하고 싶어
But what I really
want her to know
예전의 그 역겨운
모습은 나도 후회해
is the guy that
she's disgusted by,
I'm disgusted by, too.
지금은 그런 놈이 아냐
But that guy doesn't
exist anymore; he's gone.
베르나데트를 만나고 변했지
And the reason is
because of her.
우리 사이가 끝났다 해도
So, if this
relationship is over,
난 덕분에 더 나은 사람이 됐어
let her know that
she made me a better man,
그리고 고맙다고 해줘
and tell her thank you.
세상에, 하워드
(voice breaking):
Oh, my God, Howard.
내가 들었던 대사 중
제일 감동적이야
That's the most beautiful
thing I've ever heard.
네 입에서
그런 말이 나오다니
And it came out of you.
하위?
Howie?
페니가 전할 말이 있대
Penny has a message for you.
다 들었어
I heard.
너네 엄마 목소리처럼 잘 퍼지거든
Your voice, not unlike your
mother's, travels through walls.
갈까?
Do you want me to go?
아니
No.
이리와
Come here.
아직 화 안 풀렸어
I'm still really
mad at you.
아직도 화났어알아
I get that.
과거에 대해
더 고백할거 있어?
Is there anything else about
your past I should know?
대부분 해외에서 일어난 일이야
Couple things, but, you know,
most of them happened overseas.
나중에 말해줄게
I'll tell you later.
그래
Okay.
우리 결혼하는 거지?
So, is the wedding still on?
그럼
Yeah, the wedding's still on.
다행이다
(laughing):
Oh, thank God.
들러리를 할 수 있어
I'm still a maid of honor!
에라이 모르겠다
Oh, what the hell.
뭔가 흥분된다
AMY:
This is kind of hot.
Hello.
웬 가운이야?
What's with the robe?
지금 당장 섹스할 거야
I'm gonna have sex with you
right here,
세탁기 위에서
right now, on that
washing machine.
꿈 깨
No, you're not.
제발
Come on, please.
뭔가 하고 싶다면
If you want to do something,
시트나 같이 개자
you can help me
fold this sheet.
속옷 차림으로
빨래 개는 것도 대담하지
Folding a sheet in my underwear,
still pretty crazy.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==